{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496608265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496608265"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496609155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496609155"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496609752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496609752"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496610282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496610282"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496610795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496610795"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496612737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496612737"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496615881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496615881"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496632689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496632689"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496639871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496639871"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 46260690-68b8-4f85-91a0-d2bc0174c3e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496653965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496653965"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_paka_paka-kondoo-ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496659210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496659210"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-tembo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496666950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496666950"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496676833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496676833"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_songura-fisi-punda"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496681952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496681952"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twiga_punda-twiga-panya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twiga"," userResponse":" twiga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496688260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496688260"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_chura-mbwa-tembo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496693102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496693101"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496700868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496700868"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_songura-mbuni-paka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496706467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496706467"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_bata-chura-punda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496713450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496713450"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kondoo_kondoo-panya-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kondoo"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496719242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496719241"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 20a812c7-ac19-42f9-889f-4b2b0f599e39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kondoo_kondoo-panya-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496731054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496731054"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_paka_paka-kondoo-ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496736158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496736158"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_bata-chura-punda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496745650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496745650"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twiga_punda-twiga-panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twiga"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496756963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496756963"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twiga_punda-twiga-panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twiga"," userResponse":" twiga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496763139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496763139"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_songura-fisi-punda"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496779358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496779358"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" nyoka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496785321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496785321"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496790830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496790830"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_songura-mbuni-paka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496795666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496795666"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496800341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496800341"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-tembo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548496804879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548496804879"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" a990ef75-6b6d-481a-83a5-2a8f5cd9e61a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kondoo_kondoo-panya-farasi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kondoo"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506012271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506012271"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 14b0ac5a-dcbb-4ff9-a3fa-e5d089cd542a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506012952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506012952"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 14b0ac5a-dcbb-4ff9-a3fa-e5d089cd542a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506128846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506128846"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 14b0ac5a-dcbb-4ff9-a3fa-e5d089cd542a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506138985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506138985"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuzi"," userResponse":" mbuzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506145938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506145937"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chui_twiga-fisi-chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chui"," userResponse":" chui"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506162385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506162385"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_kondoo-fisi-panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506169534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506169534"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_kondoo-fisi-panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506187498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506187497"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-mbuni"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506193750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506193749"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-mbuni"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506209510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506209510"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506216975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506216974"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506223089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506223088"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_chura-farasi-panya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506230848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506230848"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyoka_chura-nyoka-kuku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" nyoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506260477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506260476"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_mbwa-chui-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" chui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506268744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506268744"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_mbwa-chui-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506273762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506273761"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_punda_simba-punda-songura"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506278376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506278376"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_bata-farasi-kuku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506284160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506284159"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9f03a4c3-69bd-4e64-bc72-6a00c0c77e1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_bata-farasi-kuku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506320567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506320567"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506322790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506322788"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506344023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506344023"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506346371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506346371"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506370601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506370601"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506373134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506373134"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506375423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506375423"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506437633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506437633"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506439846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506439846"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506442463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506442463"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506470408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506470408"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506472924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506472924"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506493205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506493202"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506493353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506493353"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506502743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506502743"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506509365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506509365"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506516568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506516568"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506590121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506590121"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 3ec8a729-fa47-49c0-b244-2d7eb5c4b970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506590208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506590208"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" afdc9a2e-6481-46e7-b7f9-648193be8a51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506618651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506618650"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" afdc9a2e-6481-46e7-b7f9-648193be8a51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506633191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506633191"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" fisi_fisi-simba-panya-mamba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" mamba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506635185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506635185"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" fisi_fisi-simba-panya-mamba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506637129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506637129"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" fisi_fisi-simba-panya-mamba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506642725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506642725"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" duma_vipepeo-panya-duma-kuku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" duma"," userResponse":" duma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506648355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506648355"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" punda_kobe-kuchakuro-punda-bata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506654145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506654144"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_kondoo-mamba-mbuzi-tembo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" mbuzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506656415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506656415"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_kondoo-mamba-mbuzi-tembo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506658377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506658377"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_kondoo-mamba-mbuzi-tembo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" mamba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506660414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506660414"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_kondoo-mamba-mbuzi-tembo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" tembo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506666564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506666564"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kobe_twiga-kobe-kuku-bata"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kobe"," userResponse":" kobe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506672009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506672009"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_tembo-duma-mende-punda"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506673936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506673936"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_tembo-duma-mende-punda"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" tembo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506678682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506678682"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" paka_paka-kobe-mbuni-chura"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506685087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506685086"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" vipepeo_sungura-buibui-vipepeo-nyati"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vipepeo"," userResponse":" vipepeo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506690944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506690944"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nyani_nyani-mende-nguruwe-twiga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyani"," userResponse":" nyani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506701252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506701252"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nguruwe_panya-fisi-duma-nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nguruwe"," userResponse":" nguruwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506703261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506703260"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" ba380efa-a92f-4ee1-9071-98e5ca087e50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nguruwe_panya-fisi-duma-nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548506718115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548506718115"," userId":" 6116002282"," sessionId":" 6116002282_20190126_125607"," gameId":" 9a21bd59-7356-436c-939e-db43620dbef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nyani_nyani-mende-nguruwe-twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyani"," userResponse":" nyani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}